Kiku, does your arm bother you?
One does not ask a samurai such things.
'Tis simply an "itch" 'til my life is snuffed out.
Much as my heart "itched" the day you disappeared...
Come, now...
Ah, if you are well enough to tease me, then all is well.
I truly apologize for disappearing without a word...
Izo.
If we do succeed in opening the borders of Wano, how do you think it might change?
Well.
We shall speak of it the next morning, should we survive.
A tall task, indeed!
We are now at total war! Win, or die trying!
We are no'doubtispread thin across the front.
I alone am enough to protect Momonosuke-sama!
Kanjuro will press the attack on Momonosuke-sama!
I shall do my best to reach Momonosuke-sama before Kanjuro does,
and fell the traitor by my own hand!
As for the rest of you, disperse and aid our allies!
It shall be done!
Aye, Kin'emon!
Neko, let us spread out!
I'mma do just that!
Mm! Best of luck!
Kin-sama!
Allow me to strike down Kanjuro!
To finish the job!
Master Nekomamushi!
I knew it was the master, ook!
Shishilian! Bariete!
Inuarashi Musketeers Captain
Where're you twor gallopin' off to?
We request your aid, Master!
Truth of the matter is, Pedro..
Farewell.
Pedro... kicked the bucket?!
Yes, in Big Mom's territory.
I believe Luffy-kun and his company wouldn't be here if it weren't for him!
Isee...
Pedro...
Ya did great meowt there!
And the person what dun it is somewhere on the island?
Yup! We need your help, eek!
Wanda and Carrot appear to be struggling against him!
Helpin' yas is a given!
Master!
That cat is flying!
B1 B2
B2
B1
1/11 / // Momonosuke-kun...
Shinobu-san.. Be wary of the Marys!
I shall use this and serve as a decoy!
111 You and I are targeted as a group.
111 And so, I shall carry this and dash like mad!
111 The enemy will believe I am carrying you and pursue me!
And then wham!, I shall lay them low!
The two of you, please remain hidden here!
Right, then!
You make it obvious that you are eager to bring the battle to them..
Off you go, Yamato.
We have established contact with Kin-sama!
I shall defend Momonosuke-sama at this very spot!
Mm! Please do, Shinobu-san!
Oh, yes!
Momonosuke-kun, you can hear Luffy's voice, right?
Is he well?
Aye, I can hear it.
It is the same as it was before.
He has grown weaker, but he is fine.
But...
N I hear only two voices now!
A duel...
Luffy and Kaido must be fighting head to head!
I must hurry!
I understand...
Herein lies everything of my father's adventures...
Oh, no! Pardon me!
Th-Therein, on pages that have long awaited your eyes, lies everything about Oden-sama.
Please, read as you wish.
Mm.
1//1 =
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm..
I had heard so many stories about him...
But to actually read them like this..
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed Y
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray ?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
B1 Don't just lay there and snooze!
B1 B2
B1
Damn, you weigh a ton...
...and suck to carry...
Luggin' your ass around ain't no picnic!
It's that guy worth 330 mil... Black-Leg Sanji!
Take him down!
Look who he's carrying!
Could that be... Pirate Hunter Zoro?!
Whadaa?!
It's a jackpot hauling around another jackpot!
Watch yer mouths!
The 330 million's lugging around the 320 million!
That's not what I meant! Dammit...
Think ya could be a little quieter about taking out the trash?
/111 You're the biggest problem here, moss moron!
Hey! Momo! Shinobu-chan!
Captain Kid!
Kid! I mean, what?
We won't let you through!
Just what I needed!
I could use more scrap metal!
Don't need the trash attached to 'em, though!
T-Take this!
Nuh?
Outta my way!
Where'd you get off to, Big Mom?!
Kid?
Oh, crap!
Must've switched us with something in mid-air!
Black Legger?!
Traf? Mossbrain?
Catch us!
Where am [?! Where's Mama?!
I'm on my way to help!
Zeus!
Where's Nami-san?
I thought you were her servant!
Hey!
Who the hell said you could kick back on my shoulder?!
At least have the decency to bea girl!
I see I got us to the right place.
Like hell you did! Where did you even come from?!
Mangy guys are not on my list of things I wanna carry! Get down already!
Ya freakin' deaf?!
Take care of him, Black Legger.
T The hell happened..?
Hold on! Explain what's going on before leaving!
Zoroer's probably got something like twenty or thirty broken bones.
Splint up his body, put him on his back, make sure he's conscious and breathing.
I didn't mean what's going on with this moron!
Mossbrain's your problem, dammit!
I've got a Big Mom to stop! You're capable of first aid at least, yeah?
Huh?!
Just handle it!
C'mon!
I ain't no doctor!
And I ain't got time for no first aid!
Freakin' jackass...
Not much else I can do, I guess...
So, tell me...
Who were ya up against that did this number on ya?
Kaido and Big Mom.
Explains a lot. Surprised you found the rooftop.
Just tell me Luffy's okay.
1 think he figured something out...
He'll win!
Don't gotta tell me that.
Anyway...
There's gotta be somewhere I can ditch you!
Sangoro-dono!
Kappa!
You guys look like you're all right! Great!
Sangoro-dono, where are you heading?
Huh?
I was gonna go to wherever Momonosuke was.
You all weren't?
Kin'emon is en route to him. He will be fine.
If you wanna help, get to the Performance Floor.
The Performance Floor? What's going on there?
Don't ask me to do something and then pass out!
Off to the Performance Floor!
Considering their strength... We must hurry, lest casualties mount even more.
Aye!
P-Pay-Pay!
P... P-P-P... Page One-sama!
Was it you...
...who burned down Okobore Town?!
Damn you!
I shan't let this pass, Big Mom!
How dare you hurt Pay-Pay?!
She's coming!
Good! We can sic Big Mom on that woman too!
* Yeah.
Somehow, Big Mom's starting to...
..lok divine to me!
Hey!
O-Lin-san!
That woman's one of the bad guys!
She's the one who did the thing that made you sad!
Whatever it is...
Shut up!
Butt out, Straw Hats!
After that tramp, you're next!
Ulti-chan! Knock her dead!
Let's take down Big Mom together!
Shut up! Stay right there! After the old bag, you are ever so next on the list!
//11.
111 111
Get moving, Komachiyo!
Get us as far away as possible!
Hey!
I said, "Stay right there'"!
Ulti-Mortar!
Komachiyo!
Oh, I have so very much had it up to here, chasing you around...
Komainu...
Your speed has given me nothing but the utmost trouble!
Busted a few bones of yours, did I?
Komachiyo...
Oh, you poor thing, so bruised and beaten...
But boy, did you ask for it!
Roll over and die like a good boy!
Dammit...!
Komachiyo!
0 O Stop it!
111 111 110 •
Tama...
0 Komachiyo's mah bestest friend!
Shut it!
O-Tama!
Tama! You okay?!
O-Tama!/ Stay with me!
Hey, Nami! Let's take her and scram!
We gotta retreat!
0 O
You there, little girl.
Laying hands on my friend, I see...
And you hurt my brother..!
You walking pile of lizard crap!
What the hell did you do to O-Tama?!
Yiliiikes!
H-Hit the brakes, Nami! We're trying to escape here!
Not anymore!
= O O  lose it when I see..=
scum like this hit children!
This hussy's getting her ass kicked from here into next week!
H-Hey, Nami!
What're you doing?! We're trying to escape here!
She's gonna get up again! ti You know how tough these dinos are!
And we've got Big Mom to our backs! We're not winning this one!
It doesn't matter where we run off to, she'll hunt us down to the ends of the world!
Worst of all, she put her hands on O-Tama, and I'm not letting her get away with that!
C'mon, Tama! Stay with us!
O-Tama, are you still alive?!
I know you've already come to! On your damn feet!
So, are you ever so ready to bite the dust?
Oh, come on, baton twirling?!
A loser like you's no match for Ulti-sama, cheerleader!
Tornado...
...Tempo!
1/1 Nice sucker punch, Nami!
But...
You'll have to do better than that!
Gotcha!
1,
I ever so never liked ya from the start.
After you got done scurrying around,
you spat out that bad joke about your captain becoming the Pirate King..
But now,
I finally get to cave your head in!
Ulti...
Don't...
O-Nami-chan...
Hera!
Yeah, Mama!
Prometheus!
Napoleon!
Go, my children!
Combine!
Ow, oW...
Maser Cannon!
First, it was Page One-sama...
And now Big Mom's knocked out Ulti-sama..
Is the alliance off?
Can you get up, Nami?!
That was crazy as hell, but it saved our butts!
Let's get outta here!
Y-Yeah..!
Komachiyo...
Sorry, Tama! Can't do anything for him right now!
We're coming back for him later, count on it!
C *
Zeus?!
Come to think of it,
who was that thundercloud?
Hey!
We've really hit it off, don't ya think, Hera?
I couldn't have done that attack with that idiot Zeus!
Oh, no, it's about you and I working well together, right, Hera?
Don't push your luck, you dummies!
All I did was follow Mama's lead.
Don't be so cold!
I begged Mama for a girlfriend, and she created you!
Me, your girlfriend? No thanks.
Whaaa?! Well, I like even that part of you!
It's nice to have some beauty around, for once!
Prometheus...
Indeed! Let's be the best of friends, the three of us!
Napoleon...
I think you lot will make a better team than you would have with Zeus.
Hey, Mama... Who's that girl?
Our former "friend" made a fine example of what not to do.
Who is she?
I'm supposed to be the one there...
Ohh...
Am I gonna be on my own from now on?
* 11
* *
That's Nami!
* 1,
If it isn't Zeus!
Oh, Mama! Sorry I'm late!
We have a new friend?
What a big relief having a fourth is!
A fourth? Oh, no, Zeus.
Uh?
I don't need you anymore!
You didn't really mean to say you don't need me anymore, right?
Isn't that right, Mama?
What're you talking about, Zeus?
You left Mama in the lurch!
No! I didn't mean to...
You've been nothing but a screw-up the whole time!
We're better off without you!
Mama!
What are you doing?! Clock's ticking!
Hera!
Go ahead, eat Zeus!
Abuh?!
By consuming his soul, you'll become even stronger!
How could you say that, Mama?!
It would be my pleasure to partake,
Mama!
Don't mind if I do, Zeus-senpai!
Make it stop! Make her stop, Mama!
I'm sorry for always messing up!
If you don't wanna see me, I'll just go away!
Come now, stop squirming!
I swear I'll never show my face in front of you again, Mama!
So I'm begging you!
Don't kill me!
Doing that would make you a thief, now wouldn't it?
A crook making off with a piece of my soul, that is!
If you're truly sorry, let her eat you, make her stronger than ever!
Have pity on me, Mama!
Serves you right!
Right, O-Tama?
And as for you lot...
I can't very well leave you alive!
Uh, wha?
It's unsafe here, so best we have you stay out of the way,
0 O-Tama!
O-Tama! You've come to!
Stay put, dearie!
O-Nami-chan! Usohachi-kun!
They're a naughty bunch of pirates called the Straw Hats!
And so...
I'm gonna butcher 'em!
11/
Wait right there!
Dun do it, O-Lin-chan!
The two of 'em are my friends!
1"11
We're doomed!
Nami!
I'm sorry!
For trying to kill you earlier!
Get this straight, Zeus! If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I hate your guts!
I'm done with you!
I'm a coward...
...so I couldn't disobey Mama!
Hera!
I know you were really nice to me, but I didn't wanna die, so I had to turn on you...
I'm a weakling... and a coward!
I don't care! I told you, we're done!
Nami?!
I know... But I ended up gettin' fired..
...and now I ain't got anybody!
1 know I'm pretty much a goner...
...but I don't wanna die with everybody hating me!
You don't gotta forgive me, just watch me!
This is gonna be the first and last time I rebel!
Tama!
Usohachi-kun!
We're outta here!
'Kay!
Just one person...
D I wanna make things right with somebody!
I'll do that, and then I'll be gone.
Run, Nami!
And know this is how I lived!
Zeus!
I'm already tapped out...
Whaada?!
Is this for real?! She's sucking out his soul!
Go on, eat up, Hera!
He's such a doofus!
Some pity Black Balls, coming your way!
Chow on these and run!
Zeus!
It's inot working! With his soul ripped out, he won't even go after his favorite food!
Eat them, Zeus!
Pull yourself together!
Thanks for being my meal, Zeus-senpai!
Zeus!
Zeus! =
Zeus...
I can feel the power surging through me!
VI She ate him...
VI
Usohachi-kun! O-Nami-chan! We gotta get away!
O-Tama!
C'mon, hurry up!
Usopp!
Yeah!
1111/
O-Tama, why are you running away?
Oh, that's how it is..
Leaving me behind, are we?!
Mama really hates deserters!
Don't look back!
And just what is it I ought to do with people I hate?
I gotta remove them!
Wha-oof!
It's you!
Punk Gibson!
Mama!
Are you all right?! Hang in there!
0 Captain Kid!
Get lost, Straw Hats.
This old ogre's...
...all-mine!
I see... Just when did..
Nah, anyone could've seen this coming from the start...
There's no doubting you wrapped yourself in Haki while we were fighting...
But you let getting your hands on a strong weapon like that go to your head, whelp!
Humans don't give up hope... No, they can't give it up...
And that's the problem..
Been a while since I got so worked up.. I screwed up.
Should've chopped your head off and declared victory...
'Cause now..
...they're gonna keep believin' you're gonna win, won't they?!
CUNIINUED